{"sid": "WM3V7Z0XUJY1_main", "calc_equals_delay": 3, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 328756, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 328757, "question": "78+37+23+47", "correct_answer": 185, "events": [["calc_7", 331993], ["calc_8", 332718], ["calc_+", 334128], ["calc_3", 334598], ["calc_7", 335010], ["calc_+", 335663], ["calc_2", 336149], ["calc_3", 336382], ["calc_+", 337110], ["calc_4", 337510], ["calc_7", 337734], ["calc_=", 338182], ["submit", 347409]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "284", "answered_time": 347409, "user_answer": "185", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "284", "question_time_start": 347409, "question": "4+24+17", "correct_answer": 45, "events": [["calc_4", 353632], ["calc_5", 353951], ["submit", 355777]], "time_left_end": "275", "answered_time": 355777, "user_answer": "45", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "275", "question_time_start": 355778, "question": "8+98+77", "correct_answer": 183, "events": [["calc_C", 356794], ["submit", 362214]], "time_left_end": "269", "answered_time": 362214, "user_answer": "183", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "269", "question_time_start": 362214, "question": "34+873", "correct_answer": 907, "events": [["submit", 369797]], "time_left_end": "261", "answered_time": 369797, "user_answer": "907", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "261", "question_time_start": 369797, "question": "24+516", "correct_answer": 540, "events": [["submit", 375270]], "time_left_end": "256", "answered_time": 375270, "user_answer": "540", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "256", "question_time_start": 375270, "question": "7+68+83", "correct_answer": 158, "events": [["submit", 383694]], "time_left_end": "248", "answered_time": 383694, "user_answer": "156", "user_correct": "False", "score": "4"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "248", "question_time_start": 383694, "question": "4+3+6+13", "correct_answer": 26, "events": [["submit", 389793]], "time_left_end": "241", "answered_time": 389793, "user_answer": "26", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "241", "question_time_start": 389793, "question": "63+13", "correct_answer": 76, "events": [["submit", 392993]], "time_left_end": "238", "answered_time": 392993, "user_answer": "76", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "238", "question_time_start": 392993, "question": "6+7+7+43", "correct_answer": 63, "events": [["submit", 395810]], "time_left_end": "235", "answered_time": 395810, "user_answer": "63", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "235", "question_time_start": 395810, "question": "59+17", "correct_answer": 76, "events": [["submit", 399424]], "time_left_end": "232", "answered_time": 399423, "user_answer": "76", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 399424, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "232", "question_time_start": 399424, "question": "4+9+9+74", "correct_answer": 96, "events": [["submit", 408903]], "time_left_end": "222", "answered_time": 408903, "user_answer": "96", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "222", "question_time_start": 408903, "question": "3+6+3+94", "correct_answer": 106, "events": [["submit", 412376]], "time_left_end": "219", "answered_time": 412376, "user_answer": "106", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "219", "question_time_start": 412376, "question": "99+59+78+64", "correct_answer": 300, "events": [["calc_9", 417134], ["calc_9", 417302], ["calc_+", 418782], ["calc_5", 419599], ["calc_9", 419998], ["calc_+", 420565], ["calc_7", 421097], ["calc_8", 421629], ["calc_+", 422247], ["calc_6", 422726], ["calc_4", 423093], ["calc_=", 423518], ["submit", 428360]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "203", "answered_time": 428360, "user_answer": "300", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "203", "question_time_start": 428360, "question": "3+66+26", "correct_answer": 95, "events": [["submit", 438013]], "time_left_end": "193", "answered_time": 438013, "user_answer": "95", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "193", "question_time_start": 438013, "question": "74+94", "correct_answer": 168, "events": [["submit", 444359]], "time_left_end": "187", "answered_time": 444359, "user_answer": "168", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "187", "question_time_start": 444360, "question": "14+193", "correct_answer": 207, "events": [["submit", 448853]], "time_left_end": "182", "answered_time": 448853, "user_answer": "207", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "182", "question_time_start": 448853, "question": "3+16+39", "correct_answer": 58, "events": [["submit", 453455]], "time_left_end": "178", "answered_time": 453455, "user_answer": "58", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "178", "question_time_start": 453455, "question": "27+697", "correct_answer": 724, "events": [["submit", 461240]], "time_left_end": "170", "answered_time": 461240, "user_answer": "724", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "170", "question_time_start": 461240, "question": "9+53+59", "correct_answer": 121, "events": [["submit", 474365]], "time_left_end": "157", "answered_time": 474365, "user_answer": "121", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "157", "question_time_start": 474365, "question": "58+17", "correct_answer": 75, "events": [["submit", 483838]], "time_left_end": "147", "answered_time": 483838, "user_answer": "75", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 483838, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "147", "question_time_start": 483838, "question": "8+9+3+99", "correct_answer": 119, "events": [["submit", 488638]], "time_left_end": "143", "answered_time": 488638, "user_answer": "119", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "143", "question_time_start": 488638, "question": "4+53+94", "correct_answer": 151, "events": [["submit", 501798]], "time_left_end": "129", "answered_time": 501798, "user_answer": "151", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "129", "question_time_start": 501798, "question": "68+747", "correct_answer": 815, "events": [["submit", 514705]], "time_left_end": "117", "answered_time": 514705, "user_answer": "815", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "117", "question_time_start": 514705, "question": "99+19+89+39", "correct_answer": 246, "events": [["calc_9", 517535], ["calc_9", 517677], ["calc_+", 518410], ["calc_1", 519013], ["calc_9", 519527], ["calc_+", 520133], ["calc_8", 520693], ["calc_9", 521237], ["calc_+", 521880], ["calc_3", 522349], ["calc_9", 522997], ["calc_=", 523461], ["submit", 529782]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "101", "answered_time": 529782, "user_answer": "246", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "101", "question_time_start": 529782, "question": "4+9+4+63", "correct_answer": 80, "events": [["submit", 537221]], "time_left_end": "94", "answered_time": 537221, "user_answer": "80", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "94", "question_time_start": 537221, "question": "3+39+28", "correct_answer": 70, "events": [["submit", 540136]], "time_left_end": "91", "answered_time": 540136, "user_answer": "60", "user_correct": "False", "score": "22"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "91", "question_time_start": 540136, "question": "44+28", "correct_answer": 72, "events": [["submit", 543869]], "time_left_end": "87", "answered_time": 543869, "user_answer": "72", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "87", "question_time_start": 543869, "question": "96+796", "correct_answer": 892, "events": [["submit", 549149]], "time_left_end": "82", "answered_time": 549149, "user_answer": "892", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "82", "question_time_start": 549149, "question": "4+59+34", "correct_answer": 97, "events": [["submit", 554343]], "time_left_end": "77", "answered_time": 554343, "user_answer": "97", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "77", "question_time_start": 554343, "question": "97+66", "correct_answer": 163, "events": [["submit", 558110]], "time_left_end": "73", "answered_time": 558110, "user_answer": "163", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 558110, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "73", "question_time_start": 558110, "question": "88+846", "correct_answer": 934, "events": [["submit", 569726]], "time_left_end": "62", "answered_time": 569725, "user_answer": "934", "user_correct": "True", "score": "27"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "62", "question_time_start": 569727, "question": "4+6+7+69", "correct_answer": 86, "events": [["submit", 575186]], "time_left_end": "56", "answered_time": 575186, "user_answer": "86", "user_correct": "True", "score": "28"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "56", "question_time_start": 575187, "question": "3+26+68", "correct_answer": 97, "events": [["submit", 581806]], "time_left_end": "49", "answered_time": 581806, "user_answer": "97", "user_correct": "True", "score": "29"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "49", "question_time_start": 581806, "question": "87+99+46+24", "correct_answer": 256, "events": [["calc_8", 583793], ["calc_7", 584022], ["calc_+", 585117], ["calc_9", 585697], ["calc_9", 585811], ["calc_+", 586210], ["calc_4", 586646], ["calc_6", 587134], ["calc_+", 588093], ["calc_2", 588528], ["calc_4", 588869], ["calc_=", 589328], ["submit", 594582]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "37", "answered_time": 594582, "user_answer": "256", "user_correct": "True", "score": "30"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "37", "question_time_start": 594582, "question": "53+369", "correct_answer": 422, "events": [["submit", 603077]], "time_left_end": "28", "answered_time": 603077, "user_answer": "422", "user_correct": "True", "score": "31"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "28", "question_time_start": 603077, "question": "6+49+16", "correct_answer": 71, "events": [["submit", 610085]], "time_left_end": "21", "answered_time": 610085, "user_answer": "71", "user_correct": "True", "score": "32"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "21", "question_time_start": 610086, "question": "34+87", "correct_answer": 121, "events": [["submit", 624672]], "time_left_end": "7", "answered_time": 624672, "user_answer": "121", "user_correct": "True", "score": "33"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "7", "question_time_start": 624672, "question": "4+37+64", "correct_answer": 105, "events": []}}}}}